

Michal Meier

S. Product designer (UX/UI/CX) & Web developer

- Design Thinking(UCD)
- User Research
- Competitive analysis
- UX Wireframe Creation
- Prototyping
- Usability Testing
- Branding+identity
- Design System

managemanet

- product Life Cycle(Lean/Aglie)
- prioritization
- sprint planning
- usabilty testing/ AB testing
- retrospectives

Education

• 2022-2024

full stack Development

Udemy+ Sololearn app Html+css+javascript, web development

2017
 UX Course
 Create school, Tel aviv

 2003 - 2007
 B. DESIGN (B.A)
 Bezalel- Academy of art and design, Jerusalem

The Department of visual communication

Contact

+972 0526026186

www.michalmeir.com

Givataim, Israel.

About Me

I work at the intersection of design, technology and human interaction, crafting experiences that facilitate conversations between brands and people. With 15 years of adventure in digital agencies, product companies, and design studios, I've been lucky enough to help some amazing companies dream up, design, and launch experiences full of value, simplicity, beauty, and ease of use. I'm super excited to bring my unique mix of skills, innovation, and enthusiasm to every project I work on!

Experience

2021 - Present

UX/CX/ product designer/ Design director

MM LAB, Tel Aviv

- Multidisciplinary design studio specializing in brand & digital experiences, Web+apps (UI/ UX/ CX) & Creative concepts. We develop modern products that push the boundaries of design. Turn ideas/problems into functional solutions to help small businesses and start-ups grow. creating unique, empathic product experiences.
- Research & analyze user requirements for design& development of nextgeneration product lines. conducting UX research, market research, competitive analysis, wireframing, visual design,& hand off.
- Interface daily with Ceo's, marketing & product managers, acting as a customer advocate to maintain focus on the end-user in all aspects of product design. Support rapid growth for the each organization

2016 - 2021

UI+UX Senior designer/ Team leader

UXPERT, Petah Tiqwa

- Conducted research on the latest trends and products in the design industry, resulting a cutting-edge design products. among clients: dominos pizza ,Leumi, Israel Railways, Pango, Hertz, Bituch Yasir etc.
- Used data analysis to measure the success of design efforts and inform future design decisions
- Built upon expertise in various tools, methodologies and processes for contributing to full product development cycle.
- Encouraged creativity and innovation to develop new solutions to complex problems
- Created a design system that improved design consistency across all product features and reduced design iteration time by 80%
- Led a team of designers to create an interactive mobile+web app that increased user retention and engagment to any product goals

Softwares

Figma, Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign, , Sketch , Adobe XD, InVision, Axure, Zeplin, Sketch, principle, cinema 4D, Jitter, fable, spline, visual studio code, trello

Languages

English - Professional

Hebrew - Native

Arabic- little knowledge

Social Links

- Facebook
- <u>Instagram</u>
- LinkedIn

Hobbies+

- Binging TV series
- Making Sushi
- Experimental typography

2011 - 2017

Art director & Team leader

Tamooz Communications Group, Tel Aviv

- Art director, Strategy & brand developer in a multidesign studio, specialize in design booths (3D design), marketing & multimedia tools for the Paharmcay Industry around the world (Among Clients: Pfizer, GE, johonson & johonson, Nipro etc)
- Project management / Team leader Creative & Design direction from Concept & brand identity until Implementation)
 UX/UI design for Web & apps (interfaces, e-panels, touchscreen etc.
- Inspired constitute of motivation into creative teams-An educator to young talents and mentoring

2007 - 2011

Senior Graphic designer

Baruch Nae creative Branding & Strategy, Tel Aviv

- The leading branding company in Israel ,responsible for creative/ strategy brand experience from concept till execution. managing brands (local & worlwide) marketing design &materials across media & platforms. Among Clients: Tnuva, Mega ,Yellow-Paz, Goldstar, Sabra, Elite, Lavido etc.
- Specialized in creating a brand identity system that included logo, website, and social media assets that increased brand recognition by 70%
- Created a comprehensive style guide that standardized the design and branding of all company materials